It was a miracle.
Yes, it would go down in the history of Mars
as The 7-minute Miracle.
This is the story
of the two girls
who were the driving force behind it.
I can't believe it!
Life has been crazy
ever since I met Tuesday a few months ago
after she ran away from home.
After playing for an audience of ten
at our first concert,
and in front of 100,000
at the Cydonia Festival, we met Crystal.
That's crazy.
Crystal smelled so good!
I've been blind the whole time.
People never notice the obvious.
What is it?
Why didn't I notice it until now?
What do you mean?
A shortcut to your debut.
It was right in front of us
the whole time.
What do you mean?
It's kind of old-school.
I see! An audition show!
Mars Brightest!
Passionate performances!
Exciting concerts!
Sparkling voices!
Performers with God-given talents gather
to compete for their debut.
That's "Mars Brightest"!
The next brightest star
is you!
If you win on this show,
you get to make your debut.
Most performers that make their debut
through the show become chart-toppers.
Haven't you seen it before?
You guys
are going to go on the show, win big,
and make your grand debut!
It's not that easy.
I'll go ahead and apply.
What? Wait!
Tell me your height, weight,
and bust, waist, and hip measurements.
What? That's sexual harassment.
No! That's what it says
on the application!
Really?
Just write something. Let me see that.
-Height: 129. Weight: 129. Bust size: 129.
-Stop!
I submitted it.
You're horrible.
First, it's the local competition.
By the way, 200,000 people
applied last year.
-What?
-Two hundred thousand?
Only eight groups get selected
to appear on the show.
Anyway, just focus on writing songs
and rehearsing.
I want to, but I'm broke.
I have to work.
You don't have to work anymore.
You got paid for performing at Cydonia.
But we only played one song!
980 Oolongs after taxes
and miscellaneous fees.
That's nothing.
We got paid!
I feel like we're pros now.
We did it!
Anyway,
I'll hold on to it for now.
-What?
-I won't do anything bad.
I have a bad feeling about this.
You keep too many secrets.
I understand you're powerful enough
to get Intergalactic to invest in you.
However, we have no idea
what's next in your plan.
You have to be more open
with your information.
When and where am I supposed to sing?
-Mars Brightest.
-What?
You're going to go on that show.
You got them to invest 12 million,
and now you're putting her
on an audition show?
Why does my Angela have to compete
against amateurs?
Angela is already famous, so it would be
unusual for her to compete in the show.
However, the show will bring publicity.
Competing out in the open
and winning with raw talent
is an effective method
for building your brand
as a singer.
However,
there is no need to compete
in the local competitions.
You'll appear in the main show
as part of a special category.
Has it already been decided
that Angela's going to win?
The viewers aren't stupid.
They'd find out if that happened.
But what if she loses to an amateur?
Are you going to lose to an amateur?
Who are you talking to?
We're here at the Alba City venue
on Mars Brightest.
It's totally packed!
Will one of today's contestants
turn out to be Mars' brightest star?
I can't wait!
They're all rivals.
You have to win against all of them.
Is this really a shortcut?
Hi!
All my followers on Mars,
are you watching this?
I'm in
the Mars Brightest preliminaries today!
I'm so excited!
Look, look. There's lots of weirdoes here.
Oh, no! I should have worn more makeup!
I look frumpy.
Hey, I found someone who looks even
frumpier than me.
Hey! Are you guys competing, too?
Who are you?
Don't you know who I am? I'm so shocked!
So, I'm not famous yet?
Isn't that Pyotr?
Pyotr from Instagram.
There's a social media star here!
Pyotr's here, too!
Pyotr's popular among female fans.
Great. So, I am sort of famous?
A few words, please!
I'm going to do my best to win
and become even more famous!
By the way, Tuesday,
you ran away from home, right?
Are you okay with being photographed?
You guys, it's almost your turn.
Oh, no!
Just make sure no one recognizes you.
Recognizes you? What do you mean?
It's complicated.
What am I going to do?
Come on.
It can't be helped.
Hey. I'm going to borrow these for a bit.
-Hey!
-I'll give them back later.
So? Can you recognize me?
It'll work.
I'm Idea, the AI singer.
I'm a high-performance AI
designed to sing!
My hobby is charging.
I'm Charlotte. I'm 7 years old.
I'll do my best to sing today.
My mother passed away recently.
My mother used to like to sing this song.
I'm a native Martian.
I'm going to sing in the Martian language.
Hi. What are your names?
Carole and...
Monday.
It says "Tuesday"
on your application form.
Which is it?
Sometimes I'm Monday, and also Wednesday.
Never mind. Where are you from?
Well... I don't speak Martian very well.
I see...
Can you speak Martian, Carole?
Yes. I'm from Earth,
but I lived in a refugee camp.
I moved to Mars when I was a kid.
So, I don't remember much about Earth.
Then do you live with your family now?
No. My parents have been gone
since I can remember.
I heard they abandoned me at a church.
I see.
That must have been hard.
I guess.
I always thought it was normal.
Can you play your song for us?
Are you ready?
Please listen.
The new manager will be coming next week.
Angie.
There's not much time left
until Mars Brightest.
Why don't you come back home?
I've kept your room the way it was.
Seeing you living on your own
makes me worried.
I won't do things like that anymore.
It happened because of the medicine's
side effects.
I'm stable now.
-Angie.
-Mom.
I'm fine on my own.
Don't worry.
You can come back home anytime.
Mom, sorry.
I can't go back.
The bedcovers I've been using
since I was a kid...
The ugly curtain pattern...
The stains on the wall...
The trophies I won
while I was a child actor...
The sound of my mom's voice
when she's mad...
Her hands...
When I'm there...
I feel like I'm suffocating.
Angela!
Angela! Angela! Angela!
Leave me alone.
-Hey.
-Roddy?
Hi.
What? Were you waiting for us?
You stalker!
No!
I was just in the area for work.
Really?
How was the audition?
I was so nervous!
When will you know the results?
They'll tell you in about a week.
Think you passed?
Who knows.
What? Have confidence in yourself!
I scouted you guys!
That's right! Gus can be weird,
but he knows talent when he sees it.
Hey. Weird?
I mean...
-Weird? You know, weird.
-Yeah, weird.
Yeah.
Tuesday, there you are.
What's wrong?
You're acting weird these days.
I came to this city
without a plan.
You helped me a lot.
But...
I still don't know anything about you.
I was always thinking about myself,
like how I ran away from home,
and don't want anyone to find me.
I was always thinking about my secrets.
I'm always hesitating.
And I don't have confidence.
I'm disappointed in myself.
I envy you, Carole.
I wish I could be you, Carole.
I get overwhelmed
by my own problems sometimes, too.
I don't open up to just anyone.
I can tell you what I really think
because of who you are, Tuesday.
And when you're singing,
you look like you're having fun.
You come alive.
Maybe you don't notice it yourself,
though.
Hey, Carole.
I don't have
many memories of my father either.
My parents divorced when I was small.
I haven't seen him for a long time.
Yeah.
My mom is a politician.
No way! That's terrible!
It is terrible!
By the way, my brother goes to Harvard.
Wow, he's one of the elite!
Yes.
And I'm a loser who couldn't even
go to school anymore.
I didn't want to hide it from you, Carole.
Yeah.
I hope we make it to the final round.
"Tuesday, how do you feel now?"
What?
We're practicing for when we win.
How do you feel?
Well... So...
Actually, I knew we'd win.
Considering our talents,
well, it's only natural!
Hey, instead of saying something,
how about answering with a cool sign?
A sign?
Like what rappers do.
Like this?
Maybe like this.
Hey, hey. Come on!
Hey.
Here.
There.
Like this!
With all this practice,
I'd feel stupid if we lost.
-Carole.
-Yeah?
I'm not going to be afraid
of being recognized anymore.
I'm here because
I want to make music with you.
I'm not doing anything wrong.
I want to be bold about it.
Yeah.
What are you going to do
if your scary politician mom finds out?
Well, when it comes to it...
whatever happens, happens!
Like a real tough guy!
All right.
I have some good news and some bad news.
What should I start with?
-What do you think?
-I'll be shocked if we lost.
But don't you want to know
the results first?
All right.
The bad news first.
Please.
You guys are going to
have to work again.
What?
Your payment for the Cydonia Festival,
980 Oolongs, is all gone.
I wanted to grow the money
for funding your activities.
But the dog wouldn't run!
Hold on. What did you do?
I lost it all betting in a dog race.
-No way!
-That's not funny!
The good news next.
To tell you the truth...
I heard about it! You passed the
Mars Brightest prelims!
What?
You're one of the eight finalists!
-No way.
-Really?
Roddy!
We did it!
I was just about to say that!
Sorry.
It's the TV station!
No way!
They're here already?
Hey, wait.
Your sunglasses!
I don't need them anymore.
Congratulations on making it
to the final round!
How does it feel to have won
out of 200,000 contestants?
Yeah.
Subtitle translation by Hoday Stearns